www.linkedin.com/in/vzottmann

Victor Zottmann

www.github.com/victorzottmann

Frontend Developer

www.victorzottmann.com

SUMMARY

Dedicated frontend developer with 1.5 years of experience and a multidisciplinary background. With a keen eye for design, Victor seeks to acquire further frontend skills to enhance interactions and elevate user experiences, while also exploring related disciplines to broaden his expertise in web development.

SKILLS

Technical Skills:

- Proficient: JavaScript, React, Node.js, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Git / GitHub
- · Familiar: TypeScript, Bash, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Unit Testing, Jira, Confluence, Bitbucket

Soft Skills:

Teamwork, Positive Attitude, Problem Solving, Strong Communication, Strong Work Ethic, Critical Thinking

EMPLOYMENT

Engineering Intern Audinate Dec 2022 - Feb 2023

- · Streamlined development processes by successfully replacing a deprecated API responsible for file storage management within the company's database system using React, MongoDB, and Node.js.
- Wrote unit tests in the Mocha testing framework to ensure data integrity when uploading and downloading files.

Engineering Intern Audinate Mar 2022 - Sep 2022

- Enhanced an internal customer support platform by integrating multi-language support using the React Intl API with TypeScript.
- Designed wireframes to aid engineers in improving the usability of the customer support platform.
- Helped product owners and managers refine customer requirements by developing practical user stories.

Research and Development Intern

Audinate

- In collaboration with an external client, participated in comprehensive testing of a proprietary desktop application, ensuring its smooth and successful release to market.
- · Played an integral role in the design thinking process and wireframe prototyping of a new product, contributing valuable insights to its development.

EDUCATION

Sydney, NSW University of Technology Sydney

Feb 2022 - Dec 2023

Master of Interaction Design (Extension) - GPA: 6.44 / 7

· Major: Interaction Programming Awards: Dean's List Engineering 2023

RECENT PROJECTS

Personal Website: www.victorzottmann.com (for additional information and projects)

Car Rental System (Website: https://victorz-car-rental.netlify.app/)

- Developed a website using HTML, CSS and JavaScript that allows users to rent cars on display.
- Utilized: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, Local Storage, Bootstrap.

Arduino Memory Game (Demo: https://youtu.be/zJscLV0aoM8)

- · Built a physical prototype of a memory game using Arduino and electronic components.
- · Tested the product with real users to improve upon usability issues found in the first design iteration.
- Utilized: Arduino, C++, Soldering Tools.

victor@victorzottmann.com